A young girl knows the truth. Now that truth is
haunting her, and someone is hunting her.
Deadly Hero is a drama, thriller, crime film directed by Ivan Nagy.
Officer Lacy is an 18-year veteran of the New York Police Department who finds himself demoted from
detective back to patrol duty for his violent tendencies and trigger-happy behavior.
Edward A. Lacy, played by Don Murray.
Sally Deveraux, played by Diahn Williams.
Rabbit Shazam, played by James Earl Jones.
Edna Broderick, played by Lilia Skala.
Reilly, played by George S. Irving.
Billings, played by Treat Williams.
Deadly Hero is a 1975 American neo noir thriller film starring Don Murray, Diahn
Williams, James Earl Jones, Lilia Skala and Treat Williams in his film debut.
It was directed by Ivan Nagy from a screenplay by
George Wislocki and Don Petersen.
Released in limited locales in 1975 with an R rating from the Motion Picture
Association of America, it was distributed by AVCO Embassy.
It opened to mixed, mostly negative reviews, and
was considered a commercial failure.
The tone is intense and dark and emotional.